[♪♪]
I'm Peppa Pig.
[SNORTS]
This is my little brother
George.
[SNORTS]
This is Mommy Pig.
And this is Daddy Pig.
[SNORTS]
[ALL LAUGHING]
Peppa Pig.
[SNORTS]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
[HORN HONKING]
NARRATOR:
Mr. Zebra the Postman
is delivering a letter
to Peppa's house.
Zoë Zebra is with
her daddy today.
She has her own letters
to deliver.
Hmm. Danny Dog, Suzy Sheep,
Rebecca Rabbit.
Ah, Peppa and George.
Just these ones left.
Good.
Let's get them delivered.
ZOE:
Yes, Daddy.
Post!
[BOTH GIGGLE]
Peppa and George love it
when the post arrives.
We've got two letters.
This one's for Daddy Pig.
How exciting.
"Dear Mr. Pig,
please pay your telephone bill."
Oh.
What's a bill?
It sounds very boring.
[LAUGHS]
Bills are very boring.
Mommy, is the other letter
for you?
No. This one's for
"Peppa and George."
Wow!
A letter for George and me.
"Please come
to my birthday party.
Love, Zoë Zebra."
Zoë Zebra has invited
Peppa and George
to her birthday party.
Yippee!
[BOTH GIGGLE]
You need to write a reply
to Zoë,
to tell her you are coming
to her party.
Can you help us write it,
Mommy?
Of course.
Peppa and George are writing
a reply to Zoë.
[SNORTS]
What would you like to say?
Dear Zoë.
Dear Zoë...
Um... I don't know what
to say next.
How about, "We would love
to come to your party.
Kind regards,
Peppa and George."
[BOTH GIGGLE]
What color envelope
shall we use?
The red one.
Miss Zoë Zebra.
DADDY PIG:
And, last of all, the stamp.
[GIGGLING]
The letter is ready
to be posted.
This is the post box.
Here are Danny, Suzy, Pedro,
Rebecca, and Emily Elephant.
[MEOWS]
They are all posting letters.
[ALL LAUGHING]
And here is Peppa,
with her letter.
There.
Now what happens?
[HORN HONKING]
Hello, everyone.
Hello, Peppa.
Did you get my letter
about my party?
Yes. And I've written you
a reply.
Oh, goody.
My goodness.
So many letters today.
And this letter is mine.
It is very,
very, important.
Is it for me?
Can I open it now?
It is for you, Zoë.
But it must be delivered
before you can open it.
That's how post works.
Oh.
And with so many letters
to deliver today,
I'd better make a start.
Can George and I
come along too?
Hop aboard, Peppa and George.
See you later.
Peppa and George are helping
Mr. Zebra deliver the post.
[♪♪]
This is Zoë Zebra's house.
This letter is addressed
to Miss Zoë Zebra.
Miss Zoë Zebra.
Zoë Zebra.
Oh! All the post
is for Zoë.
That's my letter.
Can I post it?
Certainly.
[GIGGLES]
Peppa loves posting letters.
Mommy, look.
All these letters
are for me.
Oh, amazing.
Can you read it,
Mommy?
"Dear Zoë, I would love
to come to your party.
From, Danny Dog.
Suzy Sheep's coming
to your party too.
And Rebecca, Pedro,
Emily, Candy.
They're all coming
to your party.
[SNORTS]
And this letter is from me.
It says, "We are coming
to your party.
Love and kisses,
Peppa and George."
[GIGGLES]
[DOORBELL RINGS]
Everyone has arrived
for Zoë's party.
ALL:
Happy birthday, Zoë!
Wow.
So many presents.
You'll be writing lots
of thank you letters, Zoë.
[SIGHS]
And who's going to deliver
all those
thank-you letters?
You are, Daddy.
[LAUGHS]
But I can help.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[♪♪]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
It is early morning.
Mommy and Daddy Pig
are still asleep.
[SNORING]
[BOTH GIGGLING]
Wakey, wakey,
Mommy and Daddy!
[GRUNTS]
What?
It's time to get up.
It's much too early.
Don't you know
what time it is, Peppa?
No, Daddy.
Our clock doesn't work.
Oh, dear.
Let's see if we can mend it.
[♪♪]
Ah.
The old cuckoo clock.
Why is it called
a cuckoo clock?
[SNORTS]
There's a little wooden bird
inside called a cuckoo.
I've never seen
the cuckoo.
That's because we stopped
winding it a long time ago.
The cuckoo got a bit
annoying.
Oh. Can we wind it up again,
please?
[SNORTS]
All right.
Daddy Pig's winding up
the cuckoo clock.
There.
Daddy Pig sets the clock
to the right time.
It is nearly 9:00.
Daddy, can we see
the cuckoo now?
[SNORTS]
You'll see the cuckoo soon.
What does she look like,
Daddy?
Now let me think.
She moves her head
like this:
[BOTH LAUGH]
[SNORTS]
And she flaps her wings
like this:
[BOTH LAUGHING]
And she says, ahem,
"Cuckoo!"
[BOTH LAUGHING]
[SNORTS THEN CUCKOOS]
[ALL LAUGHING]
What a noisy little cuckoo
you are, George.
[CUCKOOS THEN GIGGLES]
[RATTLING]
Look!
It's going to do
something.
[CUCKOOING]
Wow.
[GIGGLING]
Silly George.
You missed the cuckoo.
[CRYING]
The cuckoo was really,
really brilliant.
She went, "Cuckoo!"
And you missed it.
[CRYING]
Never mind, George.
You can see cuckoo
next time.
But you'll have to wait.
Cuckoo only comes out
once an hour.
Waiting is boring.
Come on, George,
let's play outside.
George does not want
to play outside.
He is waiting
to see cuckoo.
[TICKING]
It is nearly 10:00.
George has been waiting
for cuckoo for almost an hour.
George, come and play.
Mr., Dinosaur wants you
to play too.
[GROWLS]
Grr! Dinosaur.
[CUCKOOING]
George has missed
cuckoo again.
[CRYING]
Never mind, George.
Why don't you play
in the garden?
I'll call you
when it's time to see cuckoo.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
To you, George.
[GIGGLES]
[BOTH LAUGH]
[TICKING]
It is nearly 11:00.
Peppa! George!
Time to see cuckoo.
Quick, George.
You can't miss cuckoo again.
Oh.
George is running faster
than he has ever run
before.
[RATTLING]
[PANTING]
[CUCKOOING]
[LAUGHING]
George, did you see cuckoo?
Cuckoo. Cuckoo.
[GIGGLES]
BOTH:
Cuckoo!
Peppa and George
love playing cuckoos.
Cuckoo.
[GIGGLES]
It is nighttime.
GEORGE:
Cuckoo. Cuckoo.
Peppa and George
are very sleepy.
Cuckoo.
[YAWNS]
Peppa and George are asleep.
[RATTLING]
[CUCKOOING]
Aah!
Is it morning already?
Uh, no. Time to sleep.
Cuckoo is not very well.
He just needs to sleep,
like you and George.
Good night.
Good night,
my little piggies.
George, I know
how to make Cuckoo better.
[SNORTS]
We'll wind him up
like Daddy did.
[RATTLING]
[GIGGLING]
Mommy and Daddy
are fast asleep.
[BED SPRINGS CREAKING]
What?
Mommy.
Daddy. We've got something
to show you.
We've made cuckoo better.
[CUCKOOING]
[SHRIEK]
[ALL LAUGHING]
[SNORTS]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and her family
are going ice skating today.
[SNORTS]
This will be fun.
Peppa and George have never
been ice skating before.
Now, George, you won't be
very good at ice skating,
so just do what I do.
[LAUGHS]
I'm sure we'll all be very good.
Yes. Especially me.
[BOTH LAUGH]
[SNORTS]
First we need some skates.
At the ice rink,
everyone wears skates.
[SNORTS]
Hello, Miss Rabbit.
[SQUEAKS]
Hello, Mommy Pig.
We'd like to hire
some skates, please.
There you go.
ALL:
Thank you.
Happy skating.
[BOTH GIGGLE]
Here are Suzy Sheep,
Rebecca Rabbit,
Danny Dog, Zoë Zebra,
Candy Cat, Emily Elephant,
and Pedro Pony.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Peppa's friends can ice-skate
very well.
[NEIGHS]
[SNORTS]
Peppa wants to ice-skate too.
Aah!
Hello, everyone.
ALL:
Hello, Peppa!
[BLEATS AND LAUGHS]
Is this your first time
skating?
[SNORTS]
Yes.
Shall I show you
how to skate?
No, thank you, Suzy,
I'm sure I can already do it.
Okay, come on then.
Ooh.
Aah! Ugh.
[ALL LAUGHING]
This is impossible.
I don't want to do ice-skating
any more.
Don't worry, Peppa,
everyone falls over
when they ice skate.
Even I fall over.
Watch this.
Oopsy daisy.
[LAUGHS]
Silly Daddy.
[BOTH LAUGH]
George would you like
to skate?
No.
George has never
ice-skated before
and he is a bit worried.
I'll look after George
while you teach Peppa
how to skate.
Skating is easy, Peppa.
Just push with your feet
and glide.
Push, push, glide. See?
Push, push, glide.
[GIGGLES]
This is easy.
[SNORTS]
I can do it
on my own now, Mommy.
[GIGGLES]
Push, push, glide.
Well done, Peppa.
[GIGGLING AND SNORTING]
Look at me! I'm skating!
[SNORTS]
Peppa is doing
really well.
Yes.
I'm a very good teacher.
[♪♪]
[GIGGLING]
Slow down, Peppa.
You'll bump into someone.
Don't worry, Mommy.
I'm very good at skating.
Oh, where are the brakes?
Oh, dear. I forgot
to teach Peppa how to stop.
Oh.
Aah! I can't stop!
Look out!
ALL:
Whoa!
[ALL LAUGHING]
[SNORTS]
Mommy Pig taught you
to skate,
but I taught you
how to fall over.
Yes.
I'm very good
at falling over.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[SNORTS]
George?
Do you want to skate too?
No.
Come on, George.
It's fun.
I'll teach you.
[CLEARS THROAT]
First, you need to...
Whee!
George, come back.
I'm teaching you
how to ice-skate.
[GIGGLING]
What a surprise.
George can skate beautifully.
Wow! Look at George.
ALL:
Ooh.
Very good, George.
[SNORTS]
Now you need to learn
how to stop.
[COUGHS]
[GIGGLES]
Well done, George.
You're fantastic, George.
Yes. You did very well,
George, for your first lesson.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
[SNORTS]
Come on, let's skate.
ALL:
Yes.
[GIGGLING]
Peppa and George
love ice-skating.
Everyone loves
ice-skating.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[SNORTS]
Mommy and Daddy taught me
how to skate,
but I taught George.
[GIGGLES]
[SNORTS THEN LAUGHS]
[ALL LAUGHING]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and George are playing
in the garden.
Oh.
The grass has not been cut
for a while.
It has grown very long.
Come on, George.
[GEORGE GIGGLING
AND SNORTING]
PEPPA:
George, where are you?
[SNORTS]
I can't see you.
[GIGGLES]
George,
I'm coming to get you.
[GEORGE GIGGLING]
Peppa and George cannot
see each other.
[BOTH GIGGLING]
[BOTH LAUGH]
Peppa and George love playing
in the long grass.
Daddy Pig is going to read
his newspaper.
Ah, what a nice day
for doing nothing.
Daddy Pig loves
doing nothing.
Oh, goodness me,
Daddy Pig.
We've let the garden
get a bit out of control.
[SNORTS]
What do you mean, Mommy Pig?
The grass.
It needs cutting.
DADDY PIG:
Oh, I quite like it.
It's the wild garden look.
[GIGGLING]
Mommy, Daddy, come and play
in the long grass.
[SNORTS]
It's fun.
[LAUGHS]
Okay.
Let's all play
with this spotty ball.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
Oh.
[SNORTS]
Where's it gone?
The ball is lost
in the long grass.
Now we'll never find it.
Hmm. Maybe it is time
to cut the grass.
Yes, Daddy Pig.
[SNORTS]
I'll get the lawn mower.
I'm sure it's here
somewhere.
[CRASHING AND CLANGING]
Ah! Here it is.
Daddy Pig has found
the lawn mower.
[SNORTS]
It's a bit old and rusty.
Nonsense. It'll have the grass
cut in no time.
[CLANGING AND CREAKING]
[GRUNTING]
It does seem a bit rusty.
Maybe I should phone
Grandpa Pig
and ask if we can borrow
his lawnmower.
There's no need
to phone Grandpa.
I just need to push
a bit harder. Hmm.
Daddy Pig's lawn mower
is not very good.
[CREAKING]
Oh.
I know, let's phone Grandpa.
[RINGING]
Hello, Grandpa Pig
speaking.
Hello, Grandpa Pig.
Could you help us
cut some very long grass?
Oh, ha-ha! Certainly.
I'll be over right away.
Bye.
I think this is a job
for Betsy.
[♪♪]
[HORN HONKS]
Grandpa Pig is driving
his motor mower
over to Peppa's house.
[HORNS HONKING]
[SNORTS]
Grandpa Pig!
[SPEAKS GIBBERISH]
[SNORTS]
Hello, everyone.
I hear there's some grass
that needs cutting.
And it's just a bit too long
for my lawn mower.
[SNORTS]
Don't worry.
Betsy will have it done
in no time.
Is your lawn mower
called Betsy?
She certainly is.
[HORN HONKS]
[LAUGHS]
Hello, Betsy.
[HORN HONKS]
[ALL LAUGH]
Grandpa,
can we ride on Betsy?
Of course you can.
Hop aboard.
Aye, aye, Captain Grandpa.
[SNORTS]
We'll have this grass
cut in no time.
Hold tight. Here we go.
ALL:
Whee!
[LAUGHS]
[WHIRRING]
Betsy is very good
at cutting grass.
[LAUGHS]
This is fun.
[GIGGLING]
[♪♪]
There. Finished.
Grandpa,
you've missed a bit.
GRANDPA PIG:
Oh, yes.
What's this?
Oh. The spotty ball.
[GIGGLES]
Thank you for finding our ball,
Grandpa.
And thank you
for cutting the grass.
Cutting grass is easy
with Betsy.
[HORN HONKS]
[ALL LAUGHING]
[SNORTS]
Now we can play
with our spotty ball.
[GIGGLES]
To you, Daddy.
The ball bounces very well
on the short grass.
[CHUCKLES]
To you, George.
[GIGGLING]
[SPEAKS GIBBERISH]
[LAUGHS]
Catch.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[♪♪]
PEPPA:
♪ Peppa Pig ♪
[SNORTS AND GIGGLES]
[SNORTING AND GIGGLING]
♪ Peppa Pig ♪
[GIGGLING]